<HTMLQuestion xmlns="http://mechanicalturk.amazonaws.com/AWSMechanicalTurkDataSchemas/2011-11-11/HTMLQuestion.xsd"><HTMLContent>&amp;lt;!doctype html&amp;gt;&amp;lt;html lang="en"&amp;gt;&amp;lt;head&amp;gt;&amp;lt;meta charset="utf-8"/&amp;gt;&amp;lt;link rel="icon" href="https://bsc2022-usageinfo-labelling-tool.s3.eu-central-1.amazonaws.com/favicon.ico"/&amp;gt;&amp;lt;meta name="viewport" content="width=device-width,initial-scale=1"/&amp;gt;&amp;lt;meta name="theme-color" content="#000000"/&amp;gt;&amp;lt;meta name="description" content="Web site created using create-react-app"/&amp;gt;&amp;lt;link rel="apple-touch-icon" href="https://bsc2022-usageinfo-labelling-tool.s3.eu-central-1.amazonaws.com/logo192.png"/&amp;gt;&amp;lt;link rel="manifest" href="https://bsc2022-usageinfo-labelling-tool.s3.eu-central-1.amazonaws.com/manifest.json"/&amp;gt;&amp;lt;title&amp;gt;React App&amp;lt;/title&amp;gt;&amp;lt;script defer="defer" src="https://bsc2022-usageinfo-labelling-tool.s3.eu-central-1.amazonaws.com/static/js/main.4ccfe851.js"&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/head&amp;gt;&amp;lt;body&amp;gt;&amp;lt;noscript&amp;gt;You need to enable JavaScript to run this app.&amp;lt;/noscript&amp;gt;&amp;lt;script src="https://assets.crowd.aws/crowd-html-elements.js"&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div id="source" style="display:none"&amp;gt;["Great.", "This one was for me. It is perfect! All of my &amp;amp;#34;stuff&amp;amp;#34; fits. I am so excited about making some pics.", "Nice tripod while it worked, but soon after buying it a locking button on one of the legs quit working, now I have a tripod with one leg that will not lock.  This tripod is now living in the back of my closet along with the rest of the 'junk' photography equipment I've accumulated over the years.  I recommend any potential buyer pass this product by, it is simply an inferior design that won't last long.    Follow up:  My review &amp;amp; opinion of the tripod remains unchanged.  I want to note, however, that within 24 hours of placing my review I was contacted by the seller who apologized for the problems I had and shipped me a replacement free of charge.  Hopefully, I won't have problems with the replacement, but a big thumbs up to the seller for going above and beyond in standing behind the sale.", "Yes, this camera really works!  it is easy to use and if you have trouble connecting the techs at Foscam will be more than glad to help you out. These people know what they are doing.&amp;lt;br /&amp;gt;The camera is very intuitive to use. It has great color definition and the night time features are unmatched. Thank you Foscam!", "I purchased this camera literally days before a trip to Africa. Thankfully, I had some folks insist that I get a &amp;amp;#34;decent camera&amp;amp;#34; for this trip. After some research I was deciding between the D3300 and D5300, the latter of which, from what I can tell, is just a D3300 with GPS, WiFi, and slightly better autofocus. My wife and I decided that the extra $500 (give or take) wasn't worth it given our limited abilities as photographers.&amp;lt;br /&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br /&amp;gt;This camera was great for the price. Again, I'm no pro, so this was perfect for our purposes and took some great shots. The GPS on the D5300 would have been nice, but we still are very happy with our purchase.&amp;lt;br /&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br /&amp;gt;The included lens was good for standard shooting, though we got the Nikon 55-300mm lens for shooting wildlife as well"]&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div id="metadata" style="display:none"&amp;gt;[{"review_id": "R3Q9SZS2EQR33D", "product_id": "B004LLILKK", "product_title": "Amazon eGift Card - Happy Father's Day (Argyle)", "review_date": "2014-11-01", "product_category": "Gift Card"}, {"review_id": "R3UVI4VHBE0GBQ", "product_id": "B00004WCGD", "product_title": "Canon Deluxe Gadget Bag 10EG", "review_date": "2013-02-19", "product_category": "Camera"}, {"review_id": "R9O5OXPIY20DQ", "product_id": "B004RBX0GO", "product_title": "Ravelli APGL5 Professional 65\" Ball Head Camera Video Photo Tripod with Quick Release Plate and Carry Bag", "review_date": "2014-08-18", "product_category": "Camera"}, {"review_id": "RGNYO8G61NIN4", "product_id": "B003YUEF0E", "product_title": "Foscam Outdoor Wireless/Wired IP Camera with 4mm Lens", "review_date": "2013-04-09", "product_category": "Camera"}, {"review_id": "R2OCKK11HAMTG", "product_id": "B00HQ4W1QE", "product_title": "Nikon D3300 Digital SLR", "review_date": "2015-04-24", "product_category": "Camera"}]&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;crowd-form&amp;gt;&amp;lt;input name="annotations" id="annotations" type="hidden"/&amp;gt;&amp;lt;crowd-button form-action="submit" style="display:none"&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/crowd-button&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/crowd-form&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div id="root"&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;script&amp;gt;document.querySelector("crowd-form").onsubmit=function(){document.getElementById("annotations").value=JSON.stringify(JSON.parse(document.querySelector("pre").innerText))}&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/body&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/html&amp;gt;</HTMLContent><FrameHeight>0</FrameHeight></HTMLQuestion>